CHARLES BON L. CHUA

Designing ♦ Web developer ♦ Basic Programming ♦ Supervisor ♦ Writing



A goal-oriented and skillful individual, displays the ability to manage several tasks with diligence and optimistic mentality. Aiming to leverage my knowledge and experience in a new career environment and use my skills to achieve the company's goal as a web developer.

SOCIAL LINKS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

Gmail: LinkedIn: Mobile No:

charlessbonnchua@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/charles-chua-12116122a TNT (+63)948-3944-738

PORTFOLIO AND REPOSITORY LINKS

GitLab: Portfolio: Github:

https://gitlab.com/chuacharlesbon chuacharlesbon.github.io/portfolio-chua/ https://github.com/chuacharlesbon

TRAININGS AND SEMINARS

Zuitt Institute Of Learning Incorporated: Intensive Bootcamp (March 7, 2022 -April 25, 2022) Courses:

- Front-End Web Development with HTML5, CSS3, BootStrap 4 (March 2022)
- Back-End Web Development with JavaScript, MongoDb, Express.js, Node.js, PostMan, NoSQL (March 2022)
- Full Stack Web Development with MERN tech Stack (April 2022)

Basic C Programming and C# Language (*TESDA Online Course*) - Jan 2022 Basic Web Development with HTML, CSS, Javascript (*Coursera Online*) - Feb 2022

English Grammar and Technical Writing (Coursera Online) - Jan 2022

IKitchen-Inc Product Training February 2019, Store Branch, Quezon Ave IKitchen-Inc Food Safety and Food Process Training - August 2017, Head Office IKitchen-Inc

JCW Team Leaders Training- October 2016, Chowking Ph JCW On-Site Supervisor Training and Certification- June 2017, Chowking PH (at Jolibbee Center Corp - Tower)

Philippine Stock Exchange Expo 2022 (PSE Edge)
Pru Life UK (Financial Advisor Seminar)
Leadership Training (School of Leaders Ministry - DFCWHM)

SOFT SKILS

- · Quantitative reasoning
- Critical thinking
- Attention to detail
- Good English writing and comprehension
- Analytical thinking
- Quick Learner

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Database Model
- Website Design
- Technical Writing
- Coding and Programming

SUMMARY OF FEATURES

- Front-End Web Development
- Responsive Web Design
- Database Design, NoSQL
- Semantic HTML
- Back-End Web Development

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND



Tertiary: Technological Institute of the Philippines - QC 2013 - 2019

BS Civil Engineering

Related Courses:

CS 100A: Fundamentals of Programming and Algorithm

CPE 100: Computer Fundamentals

Secondary: Saint Rita College Manila 2009 - 2013 AWARDS: First Honorable Mention, SY 2012-2013 President of Academic Club - Local, (2010-2011)

Head of Disciplinary Branch of Supreme Student Council - Local, SY 2011-2012

Proofreader of School Publishing Department - Local, SY 2010-2011

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Zuitt Bootcamp

AWARD: Best Capstone 2 (April 6, 2022)

via Postman and Heroku (server side only, see Capstone 3 to simulate the server)

ECommerce System ver 1.0

• Basic CRUD

• Working on Servers and Databases

• MongoDB, Node.js, Express.js, Postman, Heroku

Updates: May 4, 2022 ver 1.4.2

Bug Fix, Messaging System, New Routes, Admin Features, ChatBot System

Project Links

My Links

Capstone 1: Developer's Portfolio https://chuacharlesbon.github.io/portfolio-chua/
Capstone 2: Server – Ecommerce https://immense-lake-17505.herokuapp.com/
Capstone 3: First Web App – Ecommerce https://react-shopnetwork-chua.vercel.app/

SKILLS INFORMATION

• Front-End Web Development

- 1. Basic Git Version Control: Local and Remote Repositories, Working on Branches (basic)
- 2. HTML5: Semantic HTML (intermediate)
- 3. Web Styling and Layout:
- Regular CSS: Inline, Internal, External CSS (Intermediate to advance)
- Bootstrap 4: working on framework, Responsive Web Design (Intermediate)
- React Bootstrap: Responsive Web Design (basic to intermediate)
- With plain JavaScript: front-end working on DOM, User-Interface, plain JavaScript (intermediate)

• Back-End Web Development

Server-side and APIs

- Node.js: Modules, Basic Packages, Basic Events, and HTTP (basic)
- Express.js: working on servers, separated concerns/components for Routes, Controllers, Models, and Modules, (basic)
- MongoDB: working with CRUD operations, Data Modeling, Database Design, NoSQL (basic to intermediate)
- With Vanilla JavaScript: back-end working on JSON, HTML DOM, UI, ES6 updates, Vanilla JS, (intermediate), JavaScript Classes, Babel, (basic)

• Other Skills

Working on C Language

- IDE: Dev-C++
- Code Structures, Conditionals, Data Types, Syntax, Functions, Fundamentals (basic)

OTHER INFORMATION

Windows **Operating System Familiarity**

IDE Familiarity Sublime Text (preffered/default), Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio (basic knowledge),

Other Tools Worked on Robo 3T, Postman (beginner level)

• Figma Software for Wireframes of Web Page Layout and Design (beginner) Other Softwares I Use

• DBSchema Software for MongoDb (beginner)

• MS Word, MS Powerpoint, MS Excel, MS Access for organizing data, reporting, managing

databases (intermediate)

• Krita v.5 for Illustrations (beginner to intermediate)

• AutoCAD for Illustrations (basic to intermediate)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ikitchen Holdings - Kuya J Restaurant Assistant Head Chef/ Trainer

(November 2018 to December 2021)

-Around three years of expertise in food standards and production in the food industry.

-Trained a set of individuals teaching different skills in terms of cooking and creativity.

-Assigns roles and tasks to employees suited to their capabilities through leadership.

Cook and Supervisor JobCon Works Inc

Assignment: Fresh n Famous Foods Inc - Chowking PH

(March 2016 - July 2017)

• Displayed goal-oriented mentality through diligence and completion of several tasks

• Managed the restaurant branch's inventory and human resource reports

· Handled the employees' training and certification

Kitchen Staff Fresh n Famous Foods Inc - Chowking PH

(February 2015 - Mar 2016)

• Displayed goal-oriented mentality through diligence and completion of several tasks

•Time Management with Academic schedule and Work Hours

• Handled the basic duties as a food prep

CHARACTER REFERENCE

Pio Barredo Jr. (Restaurant Manager - Ikitchen Holdings)

Angelica Dela Cruz (Asst. Restaurant Manager - Ikitchen Holdings) Contact number: 09167804650

Contact number: 09271432995

Personal Details Full Name: Charles Bon Lomboy Chua

Nationality: Filipino Civil Status: Single Age: 25 yrs old Height: 5'8"

Address: 12 Notre Dame Street, Barangay Silangan Cubao, Quezon City

Postal Code: 1109

Social Links and Contacts LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/charles-chua-12116122a

GitHub: https://github.com/chuacharlesbon GitLab: https://gitlab.com/chuacharlesbon

Contact: TNT (+63)948-3944-738, TNT (+63)912-8744-545

Email: charlessbonnchua@gmail.com chuacharlesbon@gmail.com

Volunteers School of Leaders Ministry

DFC-WHM

Hobbies Making digital illustrations, fan arts, Listening to Music

Academic Background Algebra, Solid Mensuration and Geometry, Trigonometry

(1.5-1.75)

Drafting, AutoCAD (1.75, 1.00)

Computer Fundamentals, Basic Algorithm and Programming with C

(2.25, 1.50)